https://www.countyfcu.org/privacy-policy/

Online Banking Login
Username
REGISTER
TUTORIAL
FORGOT USERNAME?
FORGOT PASSWORD?
FORGOT ANSWERS?
FORGOT EVERYTHING?
Menu
Menu
LOANS
PERSONALAuto LoansIndirect LendingPower Sports LoansRV & Motorhome LoansCompact Tractor & ImplementsShare or Certificate LoansPersonal LoansSkip-A-Pay
HOMEMortgagesHome EquityWarm House LoansMember Business Loans
LOAN PREPARATIONReal Estate Loan Pre-Application ChecklistApply for a LoanLoan Payment Calculator
How Can We Help?Branches & ATMSCareersContact UsFAQsLost or Stolen CardBusiness hours: 1-877-318-3838 After hours: 1-800-472-3272Security Center
CHECKING
YES AccountTraditional Checking Account55+ Checkingfree4ME CheckingChecking Account Comparison Chart
eStatementsOverdraft ProtectionDebit Card/VISA Check CardVISA Fraud Alert --via Text Messaging
County MoGO Mobile BankingConvenience Services - iTalkDirect Deposit
How Can We Help You?Branches & ATMSCareersContact UsFAQsLost or Stolen CardBusiness hours: 1-877-318-3838 After hours: 1-800-472-3272Security Center
SAVINGS
Share SavingsPremium SavingsShare CertificatesClub AccountsRetirement, Education & Health Savings AccountsDeposit Rates
Monty Moose - Kids' Savings AccountCU e-StatementDebit Card/VISA Check Card
County MoGO Mobile BankingConvenience Services - iTalkDirect Deposit
How Can We Help You?Branches & ATMSCareersContact UsFAQsLost or Stolen CardBusiness hours: 1-877-318-3838 After hours: 1-800-472-3272Security Center
BUSINESS
Business/Commercial AccountsBusiness Member Checking AccountBusiness Member LoansBusiness Credit Card AcceptanceCOVID SBA Business Assistance Info
CareersContact UsFAQsLost or Stolen Card Business hours: 1-877-318-3838 After hours: 1-800-472-3272
Grow Your Business
DIGITAL SERVICES
Online BankingCounty MoGO Mobile BankingeStatementYES Account
Wire TransfersDirect DepositVISA Purchase AlertConvenience Services - iTalk
County Bill PayApple PayGoogle PaySamsung Pay
How Can We Help You?Branches & ATMSCareersContact UsFAQsLost or Stolen CardBusiness hours: 1-877-318-3838 After hours: 1-800-472-3272Security Center
ODDS & ENDS
Shared BranchingSURF AllianceCU Certified• Best in class Auto, Motorcycle & Powersports mechanical breakdown coverage for you.
MembershipBoard of DirectorsOur Mission, Vision and Member PromiseMerger Information• The latest information on the Proposed Merger with Penobscot County Federal Credit Union.
ScholarshipsHistoryNewsCU Campaign to End HungerThe County Line NewsletterMoments that Matter- Videos
For SaleTruStage InsuranceUnited InsuranceHelpful LinksFeesFinancial Fitness FairLink to the Scholarship Application and Financial Fitness Fair Video
How Can We Help You?Branches & ATMSCareersContact UsFAQsLost or Stolen CardBusiness hours: 1-877-318-3838 After hours: 1-800-472-3272Security Center
Privacy Policy
The policy of The County Federal Credit Union (‘the credit union’) is not to sell or share non-public information with nonaffiliated third parties. We are committed to protecting the privacy of our members pertaining to personal information we collect.
Privacy disclosures will be provided to any member who opens a new account or any member who requests a copy. The credit union will continue to collect the following non-public information from these sources:
Information from an application and other forms
Information from member transactions
Information from consumer reporting agencies
Information obtained when verifying information a member provides on an application or other forms, i.e., past and present employers or other institutions where members conduct transactions.
We will not disclose any non-public personal information about our members or former members to anyone, except as permitted by law or authorized in writing by the individual member. The same policy will pertain to members who terminate their membership.
We may disclose all of the information we collect, as described above, to companies that perform marketing services or other outsourced services on our behalf or to other financial institutions with which we may have joint marketing or other agreements in writing.  However, the disclosure of any and all non-public information provided to third parties in the normal course of business on behalf of The County Federal Credit Union will be held to the same standards of privacy and remain the responsibility of the credit union.
The County Federal Credit Union will restrict access to non-public personal information about our members to entities who need to know that information to provide products or services. We will maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with Federal Regulations to guard all member non-public personal information.
The County Federal Credit Union is committed to protecting the privacy of our members. The County Federal Credit Union will continually communicate guidelines and assistance to our members to help them safeguard their personal information.
Website Disclaimer
This website contains material for informational purposes only.  The transmission and receipt of information on this website do not form or constitute any formal relationship or contract with The County Federal Credit Union.
Persons or entities receiving information contained on this website should not act upon the information without seeking professional advice.  Any links to other websites provided only for the convenience of the user and clicking on the links do not constitute a referral or endorsement of any linked website or its owner.
The County Federal Credit Union is not responsible for the contents of any linked site or any link contained in a linked website, nor any changes or updates to such sites.
Although The County Federal Credit Union attempts to provide the most timely and accurate information on its website, occasional misspellings, wrong numbers and incorrect dates may appear.  The user should verify the information provided on the website with the appropriate staff at The County Federal Credit Union.
Thank you for using our website.  Your comments and concerns are appreciated.  We will continue to work for our members to provide the very best in financial services.
Disclosures
Usually, our products and services are easy to understand. Often regulations and laws require us to provide a lot of reading material when you open an account. And we want you to understand each product or service you use. So should you have any questions, please contact your local branch office for more information. Our friendly staff is ready to help you.
LOAN RATES
CHECKING
SAVINGS
DIGITAL SERVICES
CONTACT
YES Account
Branch Hours
Auto Loans
Mortgage Loans
Apply for a Loan
Links to Third-Party Sites
You are now leaving The County Federal Credit Union website and entering a third-party website over which The County Federal Credit Union has no control. The credit union is not responsible for the content of the alternate website and does not represent either the third party or the member if the two enter into a transaction.
The County Federal Credit Union is not responsible for the content of third-party sites hyperlinked from this page, nor do they guarantee or endorse the information, recommendations, products or services offered on third-party sites. Third-party sites may have different Privacy and Security policies than The County Federal Credit Union. It is recommended to review the Privacy and Security policies of any third-party website before you provide personal or confidential information.
Proceed to Third Party Site
Cancel
